Hey everyone, it's summer, I'm outside for a video and I need you to catch up on all the Paradise releases
because they launched a bunch of new stuff which I'm going to show you.
I'm already wearing the first piece, the black and white pants called Match Edition
but I don't think it's only for soccer fans.
But we have some new sports leggings, we have a new catsuit and the Cosmic Collection, so let's go.
Alright, so this is the new catsuit, Rainbow PU.
So we have this rainbow shine in the PU fabric.
You see that better when I'm standing in direct sunlight.
I think it's a very, very nice look.
This is the ultra version.
They have one without the rainbow shine.
So if you want to have a more subtle look,
that is available too.
And also a four-letter version.
I paired it with a belt.
And yes, it's summer and it's hot, I know.
So the question will come,
Don't you sweat a lot in this kind of fabric?
Because this fabric does not really let a lot of air through.
And yes, of course it is a coated fabric.
It's not very breathable, but let's be honest,
we have over 30 degrees Celsius.
Would I be sweating if I would be wearing
t-shirt and shorts?
Yes.
Am I sweating wearing this?
Definitely yes.
But I would still be sweating wearing something else.
So I don't mind.
Another comment that's always coming is,
your skin needs to breathe.
And I'm saying, no, I breathe through mouth and nose
and not through my skin.
That is an urban myth.
I know you've all seen the James Bond movie
with the gold paint.
That is not true.
Just make sure to drink a lot during this weather
when it's hot like this,
and maybe don't excessively exercise
to just have a nice time in this heat.
Let's change into the next outfit.
A bit more practical for this weather
is the Galaxy Sportswear.
So yes, this is actually active wear fabric.
It's really soft, it's really stretchy,
it's really thin, super comfy.
There are five pieces available.
This jumpsuit, bodysuit with long sleeves,
bodysuit with short sleeves, pants,
so leggings and shorts.
This cut is also the regular jumpsuit cut.
You can get this in the classic fabric
and in the ultra fabric and in black active wear fabric.
So there's really a lot to choose from.
This is it from behind.
And again, in the sun, this fabric is just crazy.
It's like a rainbow.
So, so good.
If I remove the microphone, I can close it.
So this is the close look.
I can totally see this at a rave, for example,
with some neon accessories and just some nice makeup,
makeup, some glitter in the face maybe to match the galaxy catsuit here. Great!
Alright the next outfit is again a sportswear outfit because Paradise also
launched the new sport leggings, striped version. So if you remember the first
leggings I was wearing in this video, the black and white one, that was a striped
version and we have it again here. There's also a combination of ultra and
and classic fabric available as striped version.
And here it combines the cosmic sportswear fabric,
so slightly shiny, with the regular matte sportswear fabric.
And I love this design, it's super comfy.
My hack for summer is to wear these kinds of sports leggings
at the office because it keeps you airy,
your sweat vaporizes faster.
They still look cool, they still look elegant,
They do not look like your regular workout leggings,
but like real pants somehow,
which is what I totally like about them.
So I'm wearing them everywhere.
And now I'm wearing the same set in red cherry,
and you can combine these pants
with the top from the Cosmic Sportswear
or the normal sportswear.
I love the Cosmic Sportswear because it's slightly shiny,
so I think this is a great match
to have the Cosmic stripe here and the bra.
There's also a jacket available.
They've also bodysuits in this fabric
because it's active wear, it's just so good to wear.
And again, I kind of love this design.
It's my new favorite.
These are even more comfy than the black ones
because they're a bit wider.
So you don't need to size up or down, they're true to size.
I'm wearing size S for everything I showed you.
And I hope you enjoyed this video
and all the noises from filming outside for once
because I am just hearing something.
I have no idea what it is,
but I live with neighbors around, obviously.
So that's how it is in real life.
So check out my other paradise videos
and my discount code, which I will link down below.
I will see you in the next video.
Have a nice one.
Bye.
Thank you.